Finding aid for the Aldous and Laura Huxley papers, 1925-2007 LSC.2009
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Laura Huxley Papers
  - Music
    - Recordings
      - Label reads: 42. Music for Zen Meditation, no date; UCLA Tape No. 342; CD
      - Label reads: A) Keychan [?] Monkey Chant: 20, Kalahary [Kalahari?] Kung Bushmen: 55, Tibetan Monks: 45 B) Heart Sutra, Buddhist Bells: 6, Zen Soika x Shoccio [?] chant: 20, Japanese Temple music: 45. Continuation of 341C., no date; UCLA Tape No. 341D; CD
      - Label reads: "Wonder [?] tapr - Verdi Bach", no date; UCLA Tape No. 418; no digitized
      - Label reads: A) Keychan [?] Monkey Chant: 20, Kalahary [Kalahari?] Kung Bushmen: 55, Tibetan Monks: 45 B) Heart Sutra, Buddhist Bells: 6, Zen Soika x Shoccio [?] chant: 20, Japanese Temple music: 45, no date; UCLA Tape No. 341 (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - Label reads: 42. Music for Zen Meditation, no date; UCLA Tape No. 342 (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Label reads: 47. One) 2001 - Part 2, Part one, V. Williams[?] - Variations on a Theme by Tallis, Fantasia on Green sleves[?], Leo - Adagio [for] cello [and] strings, Rondo - Beethoven, concerto [for] piano Two) Strauss Don Quixote, Vivaldi, Verdi, Mozart, no date; UCLA Tape No. 346; not digitized; labels reversed: side two is one, side one is two (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - Label reads: 44. Beethoven Violin Concerto, about 60 m., no date; UCLA Tape No. 347; not digitized; changes speed in various sections near beginning of tape (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - Label reads: 51. Verdi - Requiem, 1 7/8, no date; UCLA Tape No. 373; not digitized (Box 114, Folder unknown container)
      - Label reads: 49. Giese King - One, Beethoven, Waldstein, Appassionata, no date; UCLA Tape No. 374; not digitized (Box 114, Folder unknown container)
      - Label reads: 43. Blue Danube, Prelude Traviata, Ave Maria, no date; UCLA Tape No. 375; not digitized (Box 114, Folder unknown container)
      - Label reads: 53. A) One, Bach - Adagio (bad recording), Albinoni Adagio, Chausson Poem, Saint-Saens Rondo, B) Two, Ravel - Daphnis and Chloe, no date; UCLA Tape No. 376; not digitized (Box 114, Folder unknown container)
      - Label reads: A) Mozart [ Beethoven? illegible] B Shuman and Shubert [?] [many of the songs are illegible], no date; UCLA Tape No. 377; not digitized (Box 114, Folder unknown container)
  - Novels, Essays and Other Written Works
    - Autobiographical Materials
      - Drafts, Publicity sheets on the life of Laura Huxley, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Be What You Are (Is This Suffering Necessary?)
      - Drafts, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Blackout
      - Clipping on film by Laura Huxley and Virginia Pfeiffer, [c. 1950?] (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Change That Record (Managing Your Impulses)
      - Drafts and Correspondence, 1963-1964; Correspondence regarding chang in title when published in Harper's Bazaar (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Forewards, Prefaces and Reviews of Others' Work
      - Drafts and Correspondence (1 of 2), 1966-1996 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Drafts and Correspondence (2 of 2), 1966-1996 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - How to Handle the Giant
      - Personal notes and illustrations by children, no date (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Laura Huxley Biography
      - Five pages; corrections by A.H., no date (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Personal notes, no date (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - My One and Only, Best Beloved Me & Related Writing
      - Personal notes and drafts, no date; translated by A.H. [?] (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - One a Day Reason to be Happy
      - Publicity sheet, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Clippings, reviews and publicity material, 1987; oversize box (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Others' Works
      - Contributions, drafts and correspondence, 1963-1983 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Our Mutt and Jeff Act
      - Drafts, no date; Regarding Oscar Janniger's book on Aldous Huxley and Gerald Heard (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Recipes for Living and Loving
      - Correspondence, 1964-1982 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Draft of Excerpt, "Jump Into The Others Place", 1960 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Excerpt, "How Can I Use This?" Published in Beechwood Voice, Volume 3 Number 4, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Review, Los Angeles Times, 27 Dec 1968 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Drafts and Notes, [1960]; includes edits (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Clippings, reviews and correspondence relating to publicity, 1970s; oversize box (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Recordings
      - Recipes for Living and Loving, Volume 1; Side 1, Your Favorite Flower; Side 2, Rainbow Walk, no date; UCLA Tape No. 445; vinyl LP (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - The Art of Aging
      - Contribution in Part 3: The Mind, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - The Child of Your Dreams
      - Published Book, by Laura Huxley and Piero Ferrucci, Published by Destiny Books, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - This Timeless Moment
      - Correspondence and Photocopies Relating to Images Published in Book, 1982-2000 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1983 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Publicity Materials, [circa 1968] (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Reviews, 1968-1976 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Clippings, reviews, 1968-1969; oversize box (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - You Are Not the Target
      - Correspondence, 1960s (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Publicity, 1960s; includes reviews, clippings and correspondence regarding publicity activities and events (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Excerpt, "Give Something for Nothing" published in Beechwood Voice, Volume 1 Number 4, 1998; article includes biographical sketch (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Draft, "What Makes you Think You Don't Want War", 1963; includes photocopy of typed draft (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Clippings, reviews and publicity material, 1960s; oversize box (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Personal
    - Collected by
      - poetry, no date (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Articles and pamphlets, 1986-2004 (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Photocopies; various images of Aldous and Laura Huxley, no date; oversize box (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence
      - Assagioli, Roberto, 1963 Jun 13; Italian psychiatrist, humanist, visionary (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Baez, Joan, 1970s? Aug 27 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Bedford, Sybille, 1960s - 1980s (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Bernstein, Robert S., 1980 Mar14 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Bishop, Elizabeth, 1973 Jun 14 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Calderone, Mary S., 1979 Feb 22; SIECUS, New York (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Canfield, Cass, 1968 Jul 24 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Cukor, George, 1970 Aug 24 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Davis, Adelle, 1966 Feb 3 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - DeHaulleville, Rose, 1960s (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Fleiss, Paul, 1997 Jan 24 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Fonda, Jane, 1977? (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Fourth World Foundation, 1979 Apr; Fairfield, Conn. (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Francis, Anne, 1979 Jan 26 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Fritz, Bernadine, 1971 May 18 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Fuller, Buckminster, 1978 Jan 22 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Grant, Cary, 1968 Aug 20 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - H [General Correspondence], 1999 Oct 16, 1980 Mar 23; Hubscher, Sue. Hughes, Virginia Marie. (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Harvard Medical School, 1980 Aug 6; Request to contribute to Psychedelic Drugs Reconsidered (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Haynes, Renee, 1966 Feb 22, 1966 Mar 15; Huxley Family, second cousin [?] (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Heard, Gerald [Michael], 1967 Jun 2, 1968 Sep 23; Regarding; letters from Jay Michael Barrie (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Hovde, Ellen, 1960s - 2000s; Ellen Hovde Huxley Giffard (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Hubble, Grace, 1963 Dec 12, 1963 Dec 26 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Huxley, Andrew and Richarda, 1960s - 1970s (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Huxley, Ann, 1965 Dec 10 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Huxley, Gervas, 1965 May 14, 1966 Mar 27 (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Huxley, Julian and Juliette, no date; no dates / envelopes only (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - Huxley, Julian and Juliette, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Huxley, Julian and Juliette, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - Huxley, Julian and Juliette, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 30)
      - Huxley, Julian and Juliette, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 31)
      - Huxley, Julian and Juliette, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 32)
      - Huxley, Julian and Juliette, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 33)
      - Huxley, Julian and Juliette, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 34)
      - Huxley, Julian and Juliette, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 35)
      - Huxley, Julian and Juliette, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 36)
      - Huxley, Julian and Juliette, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 37)
      - Huxley, Julian and Juliette, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 38)
      - Huxley, Julian and Juliette, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 39)
      - Huxley, Julian and Juliette, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 40)
      - Huxley, Julian and Juliette, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 41)
      - Huxley, Juliette, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 42)
      - Huxley, Juliette, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 43)
      - Huxley, Juliette, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 44)
      - Huxley, Juliette, 1980 - 1985 (Box 25, Folder 45)
      - Huxley, Matthew and Judy, 1962-1963; some correspondence address to both Aldous Huxley and Laura Huxley, around time of AH death (Box 25, Folder 46)
      - Huxley, Matthew and Judy, 1964 -; some correspondence address to both Aldous Huxley and Laura Huxley, around time of AH death (Box 25, Folder 47)
      - Huxley, Kathy, 1999 May 7 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Huxley, Matthew and Franziska, 2005 Feb 23; with obituary (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Huxley, Susan and Anthony, 1965 - 1966 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Huxley, Tessa, 2000 - 2005; Andrew Reicher, husband to Tessa (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Huxley, Victoria, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Huxley Institute for Biosocial Research, 1967 - 1980; letters from Abram Hoffer (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Imperial College London, 1965; RE: Thomas Henry Huxley, medals, and proposed Aldous Huxley Memorial Lectureship (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Isherwood, Margaret, 1968 - 1969 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Iyengar, B.K.S., 1962 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Kelsey, Linda, 1978 - 1982 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Kirsch, Robert, 1963 Jul 16; LA Times book editor (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Krippner, Stan and Leslie, 1971 - 2003 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Krishna, Gopi, 1969 - 1971 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Lilly, John, 1968 - 1982; with photographs (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Lindley, Francis, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Loos, Anita, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Moore, Brian, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Manning, Hugo, 1969 - 1970 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Marti-Ibanez, Felix, 1963 - 1977 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Maslow, Abe, 1968 - 1970 (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - Mayo, Charles and Alice, 1963; Mao clinic (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Menninger, Karl, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Menuhin, Yehudi, 1967 - 1992 (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - Mondschein, Ruth, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - Montagu, Ashley, 1968 - 1983 (Box 26, Folder 25)
      - Naranjo, Claudio, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 26)
      - Nys, Jeanne, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 27)
      - Pauling, Linus, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 28)
      - Pierrakos, John C., 1972 (Box 26, Folder 29)
      - Priestley, Mary, 1972; music therapist (Box 26, Folder 30)
      - Renoir, Jean, 1969 - 1973 (Box 26, Folder 31)
      - Rhine, J.B., 1968 (Box 26, Folder 32)
      - Roes, Carla, 1992 - 1993 (Box 26, Folder 33)
      - Shaw, Artie, 1988 - 1993 (Box 26, Folder 34)
      - Sineons, A.T.W., 1963 (Box 26, Folder 35)
      - Smith, Grover, 1968 - 1973 (Box 26, Folder 36)
      - Smith, Huston, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 37)
      - Tripathy, A.K., 1994 - 1995 (Box 26, Folder 38)
      - Villani, Antonello, 2004 - 2005; release form for film footage (Box 26, Folder 39)
      - Watts, Alan, 1963 - 1964 (Box 26, Folder 40)
      - Weir, Peter, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 41)
      - Wolf, William, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 42)
      - General Friends and Associates, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - General Friends and Associates, 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - General Friends and Associates, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - General Friends and Associates, 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - General Friends and Associates, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - General Friends and Associates, 1974 (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - General Friends and Associates, 1974 (2of 2) (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - General Friends and Associates, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - General Friends and Associates, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - General Friends and Associates, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - General Friends and Associates, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - General Friends and Associates, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - General Friends and Associates, 1983-1986 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - General Friends and Associates, 1990s (1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - General Friends and Associates, 1990s (2 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - General Friends and Associates, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - General Friends and Associates, no date (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - General Friends and Associates, 2001 (1 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - General Friends and Associates, 2001 (2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - General Friends and Associates, 2002-2004 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - DeHaulleville, Olivia, 1967-1980; includes photograph of the Dalai Lama as a young man (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Kammeyer, Dian, 1971-1986 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Marriot, Sylvia, 1966-1977 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Shober, Reutie [Butler], 1971-1975 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - [last name unknown], Frances, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - [last name unknown], Rita, 1972-1976 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - "Crazy Fan Mail", undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Fitz Hugh Ludlow Memorial Library, correspondence primarily from Michael Horowitz and Michael Aldrich; with updates on Timothy Leary, 1971-1986 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - related to Laura Huxley's family, no date (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Early Life
      - Clippings and press materials relating to Laura's career as a violinist, 1936-1937 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Film
      - 16 mm film: Theda and Cameron Hall on Safari with Patrick Hemingway, no date; UCLA Tape No. 474; 16 mm film (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - 16 mm film: Laura Huxley, Virginia Pfeiffer, Laura Huxley's mother(yellow dress), Virginia Pfeiffer (pink dress), Kathy Pfeiffer, Juan Pfeiffer, Laura Huxley's niece Carolina and nephew Piero (striped sweater), swimming pool in Hollywood Hills home., 1956; UCLA Tape No. 471; 16 mm film (reel 1 of 2) (Box 112, Folder 1)
      - 16 mm film: Laura Huxley, Virginia Pfeiffer, Laura Huxley's mother(yellow dress), Virginia Pfeiffer (pink dress), Kathy Pfeiffer, Juan Pfeiffer, Laura Huxley's niece Carolina and nephew Piero (striped sweater), swimming pool in Hollywood Hills home., 1956; UCLA Tape No. 472; 16 mm film (reel 2 of 2) (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Personal effects
      - Embosser, Library of Laura Huxley (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Recordings
      - Label reads: "Eternal Sea by Lois Goin set to DeBussey's Aft[ternoon] of a Faun", no date; UCLA Tape No. 407
      - Label reads: "L. 1964 reading and practicing [illegible] or (imagination) writers conference, UCLA Tape No. 429; not digitized
      - Label reads: "2 Jump- te there doll [?] Here & Now How can I use this Question - I part", [1961?]; UCLA Tape No. 421
      - Label reads: "Laura practicing Sept 61 Love not love (talk) luminous feeling my one and only", Sep 1961; UCLA Tape No. 420
      - Label reads: "4 Attend your funeral || At. --alone [?]- Bubble || Give || A if || Air W.F. || Words Away || AROUND || Song with words [? -slightly illegible], [1961?]; UCLA Tape No. 422
      - Label reads: "Current Research on cigarette smoking APA, Los Angeles 1964 Hochbaum - Horn - Lawton", 8 Sept 1964; UCLA Tape No. 425; not digitized
      - Label reads: "Reading from my book luver & another [?] I Ch. Love not love", no date; UCLA Tape No. 426; not digitized
      - Label reads: "3 Questions and now II Part Dance || Convention || Love yourself go with it [?] to Hell", [1961?]; UCLA Tape No. 427; not digitized
      - Label reads: "L. practicing Writers' conference June 1964", Jun 1964; UCLA Tape No. 428; not digitized
      - Label reads: Help Me - Tender is the Night, Pleasure [?], Pressure [?], [illegible]; Laura Huxley, reading aloud [practicing ?], Recipes for Living and Loving, no date; UCLA Tape No. 405
      - Label reads: L and Stan June 23 -72, Jun 1972; UCLA Tape No. 393
      - Label reads: first few feet, conversation with Jeff on Sept 17 - then session of August 21, then session of Sept 17 - Sept 18 71 conversation with S. about session of 17 [?], 1971; UCLA Tape No. 399A
      - Laura Huxley, reading aloud, Recipes for Living and Loving ?, no date; UCLA Tape No. 400
      - Label reads: "Drum beats beats with Joe some other good pieces", no date; UCLA Tape No. 432; not digitized; tape is on reel backwards
      - unlabeled; [recorded telephone messages and conversations from Laura Huxley's answering machine ? Including Richard Alpert - Ram Dass, Subtle Energies and Energy Medicine Society, Diana Whitmore, Paul Oconnor spi?], no date; UCLA Tape No. 441
      - Label reads: Psychological infection Not to be caught up or Live in Fear, love or Live in fear; [Laura Huxley, reading aloud, Recipes for Living and Loving ?], no date; UCLA Tape No. 401
      - Label reads: "R Bow 1961 Becoming aware of a light", UCLA Tape No. 419
      - Label reads: Virginia Pfieffer [Pfeiffer], 3 Selves Evaluation, 5-11-72, 1 7/8 speed, 1972 May 11; UCLA Tape No. 379C
      - Label reads: Virginia Pfieffer [Pfeiffer], 3 Selves Evaluation, 5-11-72, 1 7/8 speed, 1972 May 11; UCLA Tape No. 379B; Continuation of 379B.
      - Label reads: first few feet, conversation with Jeff on Sept 17 - then session of August 21, then session of Sept 17 - Sept 18 71 conversation with S. about session of 17 [?], 1971; UCLA Tape No. 399B; Continuation of 399A.
      - Label reads: first few feet, conversation with Jeff on Sept 17 - then session of August 21, then session of Sept 17 - Sept 18 71 conversation with S. about session of 17 [?], 1971; UCLA Tape No. 399C; Continuation of 399B.
      - Label reads: first few feet, conversation with Jeff on Sept 17 - then session of August 21, then session of Sept 17 - Sept 18 71 conversation with S. about session of 17 [?], 1971; UCLA Tape No. 399D; Continuation of 399C.
      - Label reads: Virginia Pfieffer [Pfeiffer], 3 Selves Evaluation, 5-11-72, 1 7/8 speed, 1972 May 11; UCLA Tape No. 379A; Continuation of 379A.
      - Laura Huxley and unidenitifed man [Bruce?], reading aloud, The Lady of Shalott; Label reads: Rx Living & Loving; Poems; Bruce - The Lady of Shalot, 1969 Feb (3" reel), 1969 Jan (3-1/4" and 3" reels); UCLA Tape No. 17; Poems include: The Dongers Tragedy, The Cruel Brother, Are You Digging …, Unquiet Grave, The Demon Lover, Sweet William, Two Sisters. (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - Laura Huxley, reciting guided meditation [?] with music Label reads: Pool of Silence, 1971 Apr; UCLA Tape No. 19; Note on 5" reel tape: "Pool of silence practice - con cancelled, first track quite good, others are practice." (Box 85, Folder 8)
      - Laura Huxley, practicing "Yes, no, yes" for speaking event [?]; Yes, No, Yes; Elliot Mintz [&] Laura, 2 Mar 1971; 1971 Feb; UCLA Tape No. 21; Side A: L Huxley. Yes, No, Yes. Side B: Elliot Mintz [&] Laura (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Laura Huxley, practicing Recipes for Living and Loving with music in background; Label reads: Practicing Ending with Valse, no date; UCLA Tape No. 22 (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - Laura Huxley, practicing Recipes for Living and Loving [?], Label reads: Practice A -No R; L. Between Heaven and Earth, 1971 Feb 28; UCLA Tape No. 23 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - Label reads: Laura Huxley, no date; UCLA Tape No. 24 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Label reads: [Laura Practicing], no date; UCLA Tape No. 25; Note on 3" reel: "Work on space one [?]", Two-at the fifth part of the 2 ____?!?" Note on 5" reel: "Practicing Resurrection of 20th jewel(?)" and "L. practicing spac -- quotation, etc." (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - Label reads: Laura and John Lilly, 1970; UCLA Tape No. 30; Note on box: 16 Jan 1970 L. Huxley 15/16 ips 1/4 + 1/4+_= 1/2=> ? Hy bogen John Lilly" (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - Label reads: John & Laura - Gym, 1971 Feb; UCLA Tape No. 31; Note on box: "A)-John L. & Laura Arika School Gym - twice (Oscar Ishazo)" (Box 86, Folder 11)
      - Label reads: Will - other side Rams Dass, L., 15/16 ips, 1979 Nov 16, 1970 Feb 7; UCLA Tape No. 32; Box has 1 page with sketch of a man's head in red ink, and a page with 2 aphorism, "The perfect punishment for going to sleep is having to live a lifetime" and (for bumper sticker), "Don't fall on your trip!". Also a holograph note on yellow paper, "Fir (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Label reads: Dick, 15/16 ips, no date; UCLA Tape No. 33; Note on box: "Side one only - Dick - L experimenting in duet [illegible] - almost nothing. Side two - nothing." (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - Label reads: Dick and Laura, no date; UCLA Tape No. 34; Note on tape: "USC for television[?]" (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - Label reads: Michael Hughes for Laura, 1965; UCLA Tape No. 35; With 2 pages of notes by Laura Huxley, folded and tucked into the box. (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - Label reads: Laura Huxley - Introduction to Rx Breathing and Light - Birds, no date; UCLA Tape No. 36; With note on tape: "good tape" (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Label reads: E. as Light, Your Favorite Rainbow, Flower Week, 1970 Apr; UCLA Tape No. 37; With 3 pages of notes by Laura Huxley, folded and tucked into the box. (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Label reads: Forsythe, Bill, L. & Paula, UCLA Tape No. 38; Notes on reel: " Dr. Forsythe, Diedrich[?], [illegible] 1969-7, P.O. - session Nov 5, "Conv. With Bill Mc, Paul & St. [illegible] gra real [crossed out] (pho analysis) Nov. 9" (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Label reads: Christmas '70, 1970; UCLA Tape No. 39; Note on box: "Anna Palo Heimo and Friends Xmas 1970" (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - Label reads: Alan Watts in Memoriam, 1974 Jan 3; UCLA Tape No. 40; Box has broadcast description, KPFK, 90.7 FM, clippings pasted on box. Note on box: Participants: "Oliver Andrews, Virginia Dennison, Laura Huxley, John Lilly, Toni Lilly, Recorded at the Lilly Ranch in Malibu - 1/3/74. Side 2: Im Memoriam: Part II The (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - Label reads: Keith Riesling[?/Rhinehart] reading for Laura, 1966 Aug 29; UCLA Tape No. 41; With 2 pages of notes by Laura Huxley, folded and tucked into the box, beginning "Keith Rhinehart=Robert John Kensington spirit guide …" (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - Label reads: Michael Hughes reading for Laura, 1965 Feb 18; UCLA Tape No. 42 (Box 87, Folder 11)
      - Label reads: Laura Huxley: The Pool of Silence / The Buddha Smile, 1971 Sep; UCLA Tape No. 43 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - Label reads: Pool of Silence, 1972 Feb; UCLA Tape No. 44; Note on box: "Esalen Feb '72 Preparation for Pool of Silence … Paul Herbert recorded" (Box 88, Folder 2)
      - Laura Huxley, Our Ultimate Investment, typed label reads: "Dan and Laura Planning O.U.I.", 1978 Apr; UCLA Tape No. 239 (Box 100, Folder 20)
      - Laura Huxley, holograph label reads "Practicing with Piero" (continued from UCLA Tape No. 255 A), 1994; UCLA Tape No. 255B (Box 101)
      - Laura Huxley, holograph label reads "Practicing with Piero", 1994; UCLA Tape No. 255A (Box 101)
      - Laura Huxley, holograph label reads "Practicing with Piero", 1994; UCLA Tape No. 255 (Box 101, Folder 16)
      - Laura Huxley, Self Recorded Autobiographical Notes, Italian and English languages, 1991 Mar 3; UCLA Tape No. 263 (Box 102, Folder 3)